Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
DAY 89.
DISAPPEARED! CONTACT THE POLICE.
It's okay.
Rocket.
Well done!
This is how... we're going
to escape this planet.
Go to your mother.
It's for the radio?
It will help us
amplify the signal.
For you.
Thanks.
It will soon darken.
Listen to me.
It's very noisy.
NEW YORK POST RUSTLES.
DAY 472.
THEY CAN HEAR YOU
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW TO SURVIVE.
GET UNDERGROUND.
CREATUREs:- BLIND.
- ATTACK SOUNDS.
- HOW MANY IN THE AREA?
- CONFIRMED 3.
S.O.S.
Sorry.
Dinner.
Thank you.
THE HUMAN EAR.
Beautiful...
I said Nothing...
DAY 473.
BIRTH DATE.
- Do not go down there!
- Why not?
- You don't know why...
- I'm going... I will not make any noise!
Don't do it.
Please.
This time. use these
little stereo amplifiers.
It will not work.
No. this should increase
the frequency to...
28min 19 - 29min 21
it never worked!
But...
We will continue to try. until it works.
Enough! Enough.
Enough!
Enough. already!
Remember... you have to divide.
We have three.
Amazing!
Time to leave.
Don't force me to go with him.
You'll be fine. Your father will
protect you. Always.
Look... It's important
that you learn these things.
also take care of me...
when I'm old... And gray...
And no longer have teeth...
Do not worry...
- I do not want to go...
- There is nothing to fear.
I will go...
You stay here. I need you to
stay here and help your mother.
I want to go.
You stay here.
You will be safe here.
She will go next time.
They are going to hear you!
Look at me.
Listen out.
The river... It's noisy.
The soft noises... are safe.
The loud noises... are not.
Unless...
There's another noise nearby...
Strong one...
You are safe.
Let me show you something.
You're alright.
I promise.
Why did't you let her come?
Do you blame her...
for what happened?
Don't...
Because she blames herself.
It's no one's fault...
You still love her. right?
Of course I do.
You should tell her.
Your mother...
I want you to make a noise...
Strong one.
Your mother... needs your help.
You can do it.
It's okay. it's okay...
You are safe.
They can't hear us.
It worked?
You just need to rest now.
Where are they?
I'll find them.
She was with me...
She was with me and then I had
to go down to laundry.
He was with you. wasn't he?
Rockets.
- He'll still be there?
- Surely.
He knows he should wait for you.
And she is...
She is smart...
You will find the place...
They know what to do.
It's a boy.
I couldn't carred him.
He was heavy. isn't he?
Still... I can feel his
weight in my arms...
Small. but... So heavy...
And my hands were free...
I was carrying the bag...
But my hands were free.
You have to stop.
I'm sorry. I couldn't carred...
I should have carred.
Who are we?
We can't protect them.
You have to protect them.
Promise me...
that you will to protect them.
Don't worry...
He will come to us.
We can not stay here.
We must go.
He will come for us.
He will come for you!
No. you're wrong
he told me!
Do not move.
Stop.
Are you fine?
We must go to that truck.
Dad!
I love you.
I HAVE ALWAYS LOVED YOU.
SURVIVE -MEDICAL SUPPLIES.
- SOUND PROOFING.
WEAKNESS?
WHAT IS THE WEAKNESS?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm